Yay!
It's started!
Mischievous School
Today there are 4 of us!
What a surprise!
We are here in Gerosin!
Gifu Prefecture!
Geroge Onsen!
Gerogero!
There's a little pond right there.
That little pond-like place right there...
It's already a hot spring!
Hot spring!
It was hot!
It was so hot!
I'm so happy!
Yes!
I'm recording now in the middle of March.
Maybe when this is released
the cherry blossoms along the Hida River here
I think the cherry blossoms along the Nehidagawa River here will probably be in full bloom!
It's going to be great!
These are all cherry trees.
I saw some buds just now.
Oh! I got a letter!
I wonder why.
I wonder if they came.
I don't know.
Why is this Tamakan here?
This is the first time we're doing a location shoot like this.
And it's a sleepover location.
Wait a minute.
A letter!
I don't even know what a sleepover is.
It's definitely not enough for a letter.
I've already brought my luggage.
If I ask you what you've read, you'll say it's a lie and it'll fall apart.
That's true.
Let's start with the letter.
Yes! Let's read the letter!
Good morning, Team Chachie!
Good morning.
This is Staff Y.
This is our first project since the beginning of the school.
the first time!
First time!
First time?
We are going to stay overnight on location!
I knew it!
It's the first time!
It was the first time!
That's great!
I brought it just in case!
It's an overnight location shoot.
It's called "Exciting School Trip!
School trip!
I'm so happy!
I've given you a theme at the opening of every Hajimecha Gakuen, but this time, we have a mission to accomplish through this school trip.
But this time, we have a mission through this school trip!
What's the mission?
It's to take pictures and videos!
Oh!
That's cool!
Please take pictures of stores, spots, scenery, and members of the group.
Please take a picture or a video during the trip.
This time, we will be divided into two pairs.
Which one?
First, Daikoku!
Sakamoto pair!
Oh!
And Sakura Akimoto pair!
Yes!
We'll split into these two pairs and go around the town of Gero.
but you are welcome to join us even when we are not on location.
Please feel free to take pictures of anything!
Yay!
It can be a photo or a video.
Anything is OK.
I'm looking forward to it!
What's more, this school trip is going to be...
What is it?
Yukari Resort Gero Naga Nagarakusha
Oh!
We're with you!
The Longest Raku-sha
You're invited!
Thank you.
Isn't that the one with the "YUKAI RESORT" on it?
We will be taking pictures with the cooperation of Saicho Gakusha. Thank you very much!
We hope you have fun, eat delicious food, and learn a lot... so that we can make this an exciting and crazy school trip!
Have a good trip! Bon appétit!
Yay, yay! I'm so happy! I've seen the resort in the commercials a lot.
I see it! Slow resort!
I'm so happy! I've never been to a barbecue before.
Then why don't you come here on your own? Let's have fun!
Tell me all about it. First of all, let's go for the flies... as a pair.
We can go to each other's. We're going separately.
I'll take a lot of pictures. Watch me later.
We'll do it together! I'm off!Let's do it together! I'm off!
Kinkong kankong!
Brought to you from Gero with the help of Yukarizo and Gero Nagaraku!
Yay! I'm dressed now!
We're the Haruyuzuki pair. Pleased to meet you.
We'd like to go for a stroll in the city at night.
So the four of us will start off in casual clothes? Really? Isn't that new?
Aren't we supposed to be students at Hajimecha Academy? That's what I thought.
A school trip? Yes, yes, yes. Aren't all the rivers around here hot springs?
Are these hot springs too? Are they all connected? Is a river a river?
A river is a river? A river is a river.
It's beautiful, isn't it? It's really nice to come here at any time of the year.
It's great no matter what time of year you come, you'll see a different view.
There are many free footbaths. There are a lot of free footbaths.
Free? Yeah, free. Isn't it amazing? There are a lot of places where you can go in for free.
I wonder where they are? And there are even places where you can eat sweets while bathing.
What? You can take a footbath while eating sweets? Isn't that amazing?
You can use the footbath while eating. That makes me so happy.
That's so great! Let's go find a place. First.
Let's find a place where we can definitely eat. I'm hungry.
So it's definitely going to start.
Then let's feed Yuzuki and soak in a warm footbath.
Let's soak in the footbath. Let's go.
Yuzuki, here. This is what I was looking for. This?
Isn't this cute? Yumi-ya. So cute!
Hey, Hanami, you can eat the pudding there while soaking your feet.
What? This? Yes!
Hello. Hello.
Please take your choice of pudding and caramel sauce from here.
What? And the caramel sauce? That's so cute.
Hey, what's that? It's cute. They're using it for the orchestra.
The pudding is in a hot spring.
You mean it's really hot? It's not really a hot spring.
It's heated by the temperature. The temperature is set at 75 degrees.
It's very rare to have pudding that's hot and warm, isn't it?
It's very rare. I've never had it before.
It doesn't matter which one, right?
What? Which one do you want? You want me to come? Someone's calling.
Okay, I'll take the one in front of me.
Okay, I'll take the girl on the diagonal.
Let's go with these girls.
Wow, the caramel sauce is warm too.
Amazing! Isn't it amazing?
I've never had warm pudding. It's warm!
The caramel sauce is warm, too. Warm!
Warm pudding!
It's warm!
Can I have some for my soup?
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll go in... I'm going in.
I'm coming in. I'm in!
It's warm. The temperature is perfect.
It's just the right temperature. It's great.
He looks like he wants to come in. It feels good.
Oh, my God. Is it?
It's so nice, it's making me sick. It's making me sick.
Oh, my God.
Let's eat pudding.
Let's have some pudding.
There's plenty of it. Oh, no.
Oh, no! This looks delicious!
Well, Yuzuki, I'll have some.
I'm off.
Maybe it's that way.
Delicious!
Delicious! It melts in your mouth!
It's so eggy.
And the caramel... it's amazing.
Oh, wait a minute.
Look at this. Look at the pudding.
Is this the smoothest pudding you've ever tasted?
So soft!
It's so soft it's going to fall apart.
It's gone.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I don't know yet.
Come to my mouth.
Bon appétit!
Oh, my God!
It's gone, isn't it?
The state of your mouth
Yum!
What? Isn't it bad? I drank it! It's a drink.
It's too soft.
It's so good!
Why is it so delicious?
It says...
It says 100% gero milk!
Omae Farm's cherry egg Madagascar savanilla bean
Smooth and rich pudding with plenty of fresh cream with 47% milk fat!
It's so rich!
You can feel everything.
Eggs, vanilla beans, cream, you feel it all!
There really is such a delicious pudding!
How about eating pudding while taking a footbath?
It's the best!
I've never experienced anything like this!
You can only experience it here!
It satisfies the body, the soul, and the stomach.
It's so peaceful.
It's delicious!It was delicious.
It was great.
My feet are soooo smooth.
I could tell the difference as soon as I got out and wiped them off with a towel.
So smooth!
I am now a lady with smooth feet!
A lady with smooth feet!
The pudding was so delicious!
It was so smooth and delicious!
I took a lot of great pictures.
But there is one that I think is the best one for this event.
Here it is!
Please take a look.
It's a nice picture.
It's colorful, so it looks even better.
There's another one.
Seino
This is just like a footbath and pudding.
It's in the process of becoming smooth.
Here's a picture of the pudding in the process of becoming smooth and silky.
Please find your favorite and take lots of pictures!
The exciting girls' school trip is still going on!
Bye bye!
Smooth and smooth!
Shaqi News
Shaqi News!
Yes, it's time for the Shaqi News!
It is time for the Shaqi News.
Thank you for your patience.
What do you have for us?
First of all, let me start by saying that today, April 7, we made our debut on the street at Nagoya Castle,
It's been 11 years since we made our debut on the streets of Nagoya Castle.
Wow, you are 12 years old?
Twelve years old?
I am 11 years old.
I'm 11 years old. Since the time of the chum orca, the whole body group, the chum orca, it's been 11 years,
It's been 11 whole years.
Isn't that amazing?
I have started my 12th year,
Thanks to all of you who have always supported us.
Thank you very much.
Tomorrow, April 8, we will be holding a talk show called Chumshachi Twenties Talk Trip.
There will be two parts, both of which will include a benefit event,
Please join us and send your congratulations directly to the Tumi Orca Twenties. Please send your congratulations directly to them.
On July 22nd, we will be performing a one-man live show called "Orca-sama" at Nagoya Castle.
Since the days of Team Shachiko, "Shachisama" has been one of the biggest summer events that we cannot miss,
This time it will be in Nagoya and at Nagoya Castle, where we were born,
It's amazing.
It's going to be a hotter summer than ever before,
It will definitely be a hotter summer than ever before,
Please be sure to come and meet him. We have also lifted the ban on vocal performances,
Please let us hear your support.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.